Abdolreza Tehranchi

305 Axminester Drive. Richmond Hill. O.N. Postal Cod. L4C 2W3

Cellphone: 416-602-7730

Email: tehranchiab@gmail.com

Objective

To obtain a position as a Mathematics Professor in University and Mathematics Teacher/Tutor

Summary

Having taught at different academic centers and schools and Universities for over twenty years, I have developed a wide range of skills that would meet, and exceed the expectations for the role. In my present role as a University Professor for Azad University of Tehran, Iran, I have had many achievements, including more than fifteen articles published in scholarly journals and numerous international conference presentations and a few published books.

Would relish the opportunity to bring this level of success to your University. If you would like to get in touch to discuss my application and to arrange an interview, you can contact me.

Education

*PhD in Mathematics (Complex Analysis)

Pune University, Pune, India

2002 - 2005

Thesis Title: Study of Some Recent Topics in Holomorphic Functions Theory

Supervisor: Professor S.R. Kulkarni

*MSc in Mathematics (Fuzzy Algebra)

Tarbiyat Modarres University (TMU), Tehran, Iran.

1992 - 1994

Thesis Title: Multiple Boolean Algebra and Their Application to Fuzzy Sets

*BSc in Mathematics Teaching

Birjand University, Birjand, Iran

1987 - 1991

* General Arts and Since

Gorge Brown College, Toronto, Canada

2014- Now

Teaching Experience

*Lecturer

Islamic Azad University of Tehran, Iran

1998 - 2019

*	Invi	ted	D,	of	966	or
- 1	III VI	ı.e.u	PI			

Universities in	Tehran, Iran	1992 – 1998

*Math Teacher

Mashhad High School, Iran 1991 – 1992

*Teaching Assistant

Ferdowsi University in Mashhad, Iran 1989 – 1991

* Tutoring and private class for students in Universities in Toronto and students in high schools in Toronto. 2013 – Now

*Math Teacher in Pascal Academy in Toronto 2015- 2018

Teaching Courses

*Undergraduate Courses:

Calculus (I & II & III), Analysis (I, II), Ordinary Differential Equations

*Graduate Courses:

Analysis III, Real Analysis, Complex Analysis

Awards

*Distinguished lecturer in Azad university of Tehran.

*Since autumn 2002, I've been a member of the Iranian Mathematical Society

(URL: http://www.ims.ir/en).

Research Interests

Geometric Functional Analysis , Complex Analysis, Harmonic Analysis, Functional Analysis , Fuzzy Mathematics

Published Papers

- A characterization of 2-primal and NI rings over skew inverse Laurent series rings, Journal of Algebra and Its Applications, 1950221, 2018.
- Some results on skew Hurwitz series rings, Rendiconti del Circolo Matematico di Palermo Series 2, 1-9, 2018.
- Study of Neighborhoods and Fractional Calculus of Univalent Functions on new class by Using Komato Operator, Journal of Advances in Mathematics (JAM), 2014.
- On a Class of Holomorphic Function, Journal of Science and Arts, No. 2(23), pp. 141-150, 2013
- Study on Integral Operators by Using Komato Operator on A New Class of Univalent Functions, Journal of Mathematics Research,in Canada, 3(4)(2011), 67 74.
- Radius of Starlike and Partial Sum Property for Holomorphic Functions Defined by Komato Operator, J. Acta Universitatis Apulensis in Romani, (27)(2011), 243 252.

Papers Presented at Conferences

- On a subclass of Monomorphic Multivalent Function Associated with salagean Operator, International Multi Conference of Engineers and Computer Scientists (IMECS 2011)., 16-18 March, 2011 Hong Kong
- A Class of Univalent Function Many Coefficients With Fixed Finite, International Conference On Applied Analysis and Algebra (ICAAA2011)" 29-30 June and 1-2 July 2011 in Istanbul, Turkey
- Subclass of a-Uniformly Starlike and Convex p-valent Functions in Terms of Fractional Derivative of f(z) of order delta, International Conference on Functional Equations, Geometric Functions and Applications(ICFGA2012),10-12th May 2012, Payame Noor University, Tabriz, Iran

Books

- Introduction to Cryptography.
- Ordinary Differential Equations.
- Calculus I
- Calculus II

Reference

Professor Ahmad Moussavi

Professor, Department of Mathematics, School of Science, Tarbiat Modares University (TMU), P.O.Box 14155-4838, Tehran, Iran.

E-mail: moussavi.a@gmail.com, moussavi_a@modares.ac.ir

Cellphone:+98-912-4755987

Dr. Manochehr Oliyazadeh

oliazade@msn.com

Cellphon: +1416-726-2091 Professor S.R. Koulkarni

Professor, Department of Mathematics, Fergusson College, Pune, India

E-mail: kulkarni frg@yahoo.com

Dr. Mohammad Bagheri

Associate Professor, Department of Mathematics, School of Science, Tarbiat Modares University (TMU), P.O.Box 14155-4838, Tehran, Iran.

E-mail: <u>bagheri@modares.ac.ir</u> Cellphone:+98-912-7978985

Dr. Abbas Heydari

Associate Professor, Department of Mathematics, School of Science, Tarbiat Modares University (TMU), P.O.Box 14155-4838, Tehran, Iran.

E-mail: <u>aheydari@modares.ac.ir</u> Cellphone:+98-912-3888103